<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ECON0791</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ECON0791</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Basics of Excel</title>
      <link>/econ0791/1-basicsofexcel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/econ0791/1-basicsofexcel/</guid>
      <description>Visit the ECON03SEC1 website for the Basics of Excel Course. Here you can omit module 4. The rest of the modules are a part of your course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Introductory Econometrics with Excel</title>
      <link>/econ0791/2-introductory-econometrics-with-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/econ0791/2-introductory-econometrics-with-excel/</guid>
      <description>Downloads:Data: caschool.xlsx; Growth.xlsxData Description: californiatestscores.docx; Growth_Description.pdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Basics of R</title>
      <link>/econ0791/3-basics-of-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/econ0791/3-basics-of-r/</guid>
      <description>SyllabusIntroductionInstalling R and RStudio: R Versions, Download and install R, Installing Packages, Loading Packages, Updating R and its Packages.User Interface, Packages and Help: The R Console, RStudio, Getting Help.R Packages: Listing Packages in Local Libraries, Loading Packages, Package Repositories, Finding and Installing Packages Inside R and other Repositories,The R LanguageOverview: Expressions, Objects, Symbols, Functions, Special Values.R Objects: Vectors, Integers, Character, Logicals, Complex and Raw, Attributes of Objects, Matrices, Arrays, Class, Dates and Time, Factors, Coercion, Lists, Data Frames, Changing values, Logical Subsetting, Boolean Operators, Missing Information and removing NAs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcement</title>
      <link>/announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/announcement/</guid>
      <description>Send in your R scripts using the google form. You need to upload your R Script in the google form. You have to mention your Name and Roll number in the R Script as a comment. Save the R script in your name, roll no and date of submission, e.g. pravesh48_8_jan.R if my roll no is 48 and I am submitting on 8 January.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>